...and Transgender Alliance Luau."
(Sheldon:)Oh, another market to expand into.
Balding gay men.
(Howard:)And I'll bet lesbians love Bluetooth.
(Sheldon:)We should get to work.
(Penny:)Wait, wait, why does it say
"one-day rush"?
(Penny:)Since when do we offer a one-day rush?
(Leonard:)Amazon offers one-day rush.
(Penny:)Yeah, but they don't have to glue
the books together.
How are we gonna make
1000 Penny Blossoms in one day?
(Leonard:)Don't yell at me. I'm not manufacturing.
I'm just web design.
I have to call them and cancel that order.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, but was this not your goal?
(Sheldon:)Financial independence through
entrepreneurial brilliance and innovation?
Yeah, my brilliance and innovation,
of course, but still.
I just don't see how we can pull this off.
(Sheldon:)Okay, that, right there,
that equivocation and self-doubt...
(Sheldon:)...that is not the American spirit.
(Sheldon:)Did Davy Crockett quit at the Alamo?
Did Jim Bowie?
(Howard:)They didn't quit. They were massacred...